

# Linnapas Larsen

Sales Advisor & Freelance Junior Front-end Developer

### Contact

2)

+47 466 22 654



linnapas86@gmail.com



Galgeberg 3B, 0657 Oslo

# **About Me**

Creative and motivated professional with a passion for design, technology, and user experience. I bring a detail-oriented mindset, strong visual sense, and a problem-solving approach to every project. Adaptable, fast-learning, and committed to continuous growth.

# Education

BA in Arts English Silpakorn University 2005-2009

# Certificates

VM & Stylist Elle Education Apr+Oct 2022 Communication & Marketing for Luxury Fashion Elle Education Nov 2022 + May 2023

# **Skills**

- Customer Communication
- · Visual and Technical Detail
- Relationship Management
- · Front-End Development Skills
- · Responsive UX/UI
- Problem-Solving & Adaptability
- Styling, Merchandising & Brand Presentation

# Language

- Thai Native
- English Fluent
- Norwegian B1 Level

# References

Upon request

# Experience

### Sales Advisor

MaxMara Oslo

Jan 2024 - Present

Assist clients following the Brand philosophy, service and quality standards, ensure that all merchandise is properly displayed and organized, maintain and update professional and technical knowledge, deliver excellent service, handle customer queries and complaints, proactively suggest strategies to attract new customers, expand store traffic, and enhance brand awareness in the market, and act as ambassador of the customer-centric logic within the store.

#### Sales Advisor

**H&M Oslo City** 

Feb 2023 - Dec 2023

Perform customer service and merchandising duties on the sales floor, arranging garments attractively on racks and shelves, locating merchandise for shoppers, responding to customer requests, operating cash registers, placing new collections, and ensuring the garments are in line with current trends.

### Visual Merchandiser (temporary)

**H&M Karl Johansgate** 

Sep 2022 - Feb 2023

Stay updated in terms of trends and fashion, present garments in attractive and commercial ways, share, inspire and educate teams about seasonal trends, exceed customers expectations, meet customer service standard, follow up H&M materials, Commercial Handbook, ensure A-area is linked to other rooms according to the Commercial Info, follow up sales and take actions to increase sales target, ensure visual rooms are tidy and clutter-free, coordinate with department manager.

### Sales Advisor

**H&M Oslo City** 

May 2021 - Aug 2022

Perform customer service and merchandising duties on the sales floor, arrange garments attractively on racks and shelves, locate merchandise for shoppers, respond to customers requests, operate cash registers, place new collections and ensure the garments are corresponded to the current trends.

### Assistant Front Office Manager

Millennium Resort Patong Phuket, Thailand

Jun 2018-May 2019

Welcome and handle all VIP guests, coordinate with other concerned departments, handle handover and briefing to Manager on Duty, ensure all on-duty staff are well groomed and follow hotel standard, oversee daily movement of guest activities and be able to resolve any complaints, ensure the operation runs smoothly and recommends improvement in operation, manage Front Office schedules and trainings.

### Guest Services and Relation Manager

Millennium Resort Patong Phuket, Thailand

Jun 2018-May 2019

Support Front Office personnel, ensure on-duty staff follow hotel standards, report directly to and communicate with the Front Office Manager regarding guest service and hotel operations, handle requests and complaints, and be fully conversant with all hotel emergency procedures.